DALILA ACQUAVIVA

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+39 3423288413

 \checkmark

acquavivadalila@gmail.com

9

Via Fraine 87, Rome

 \bigvee

www.acquavivadalila.com

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

I.T.C.G. Enrico Fermi

2014 - 2020

Diploma in finance and marketing administration, articulation in corporate information systems.

Vote: 100/100

MASTER FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Musa Formazione

2024

INTENSIVE COURSE FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Digitality Consulting S.r.l.

2024

SKILLS

Front-end: HTML, Css, Javascript,

Typescript, Angular, React,

Bootstrap, TailwindCss.

Back-end: Php, MySql, Laravel, Java,

Docker, Sping, Visual Basic.

Mobile: Flutter, Dart.

ECDL

Problem-Solving

Strong Responsibility

Strong Communication

English level B1

SUMMARY

Both through my studies and through the various work experiences I have increasingly developed a propensity for information technology, specifically for the development of web applications.

I am a person with a strong sense of responsibility, determination and collaboration.

I like both working in groups and sharing objectives and working independently.

EXPERIENCE

ACCOUNTING CONTROL OFFICER

Estia S.p.A. (ex Romana condomini S.r.l.s.)

07/2021 - 02/2024

- Tutoring colleagues regarding the use of various accounting management software (Arcadia and Danea Domustudio)
- Maintenance of accounting software hardware maintenance
- Control of bank reconciliations via automation (CBI)
- Control of invoices automatically registered via AdE's portal

ACCOUNTING ASSISTANT (INTERN)

S&P Romana Services S.r.l.s

01/2021 - 07/2021

- Training courses on accounting management (Danea Domustudio)
- Inserting journal entries
- Customer reception
- Active and passive electronic invoicing

Dafifa Acquaviva